vero.co 2019-07-15

# Privacy Policy — VERO™ – True Social

Welcome to Vero True Social, the online and mobile service of Vero Labs, Inc. (“ **Vero** ,” “ **we** ,” or “ **us** ”).  Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our Service, and your choices about the collection and use of your information. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our [Terms of Use](https://vero.co/terms-of-use).

Our Privacy Policy is designed to be accessible and honest about our privacy practices and principles. That’s why we provided the plain-English explanation of the Privacy Policy to the right. While the explanation is not part of the legal Privacy Policy (and therefore non-binding), we hope it will help you navigate this policy more easily. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at any time at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c8aca9bca9b8baa1bea9abb188beadbaa7e6aba7). 

For the purposes of EU data protection laws ("Data Protection Legislation"), Vero is the data controller (i.e. the company which is responsible for, and controls the processing of, your personal data). 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**_What Information We Collect From You:_ Information you provide us directly:** We ask for certain information such as your username, first and last name, phone number and email address when you register for a Vero account or if you correspond with us. We may also collect your photo and government ID to validate your identity, if you have asked us to do so such as if you request to verify your account. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service, and may collect User Content you post to the Service. User Content can be made publicly available if you choose to do so - we operate a feature that allows you to share a link to your profile where your posts can be viewed publicly by non-users of the Service. We may also allow you to provide us your log-in credentials for third-party services (like Twitter) so that you can post information from the Service onto the third-party service. 

**Inviting a contact to use Vero from the “Add Contacts” feature:** If you choose to use our invitation service to invite a third party to the Service through our “Invite friends” feature, we may access and collect information from your address book available on your mobile device and/or your email account, with your permission, in order to find your contacts on the Service. You understand that by inviting a contact to Vero through the “Invite friends” feature, you are directly sending a text or email from your personal accounts. In addition, you understand and agree that normal carrier charges apply to communications sent from your phone. Since this invitation is coming directly from your email or phone, we do not have access to or control this communication. 

**Adding Contacts on the Service:** If you choose, you can find people you know with Vero accounts through our “Add Contacts” feature or by searching names and usernames on Vero. The “Add Contacts” feature may allow you to choose to find contacts either through your address book or through a search of names and usernames on Vero. If you choose to add your contacts through your address book, then you agree to provide Vero access to your address book such that we can regularly perform the search necessary to determine whether or not someone associated with the information you provide (including new contacts as you add them) is using Vero. If you choose to add your contacts through social media sites, then you understand that the information these sites provide to us to conduct this type of search is governed by their privacy policies and your account settings on those sites. If you choose to add your contacts through a search of names or usernames then simply type a name to search and see if that name or username appears on our Service. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

You provide information about yourself when you sign up for an account, including your name and email-address. When you communicate through the Service, we may keep copies of those communications. You can also provide content to display on the Service. You may also provide us your credentials for third-party services (like Twitter) so you can post information from our Service onto those other services. 

You can expand your Vero network on the Service by inviting your contacts in your address book and by finding existing users through the search function on the Service. When you invite your contacts in your address book, you give Vero permission to access your address book and send invitation emails or texts from your phone to those contacts you choose to invite to the Service and _only those contacts._

 **Information we may receive from third parties:** We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, by “following,” “liking,” adding the Vero application, linking your account to the Vero Service, etc., a third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to Vero. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. If you allow us access to your address book, your contacts’ user IDs, and your connection to those contacts, may be used and stored to make your experience more social, and to allow you to add your contacts on the Service as well as provide you with updates if and when your contacts join Vero. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Vero Service. You may also unlink your third party account from the Service by adjusting your settings on the third party service. If you unlink your third party account, we will remove the information collected about you in connection with that service. 

When you interact with us and our accounts on third-party services, we may receive information about you from those third parties. You can control the information we receive through the settings on those third-party services or by unlinking your Vero account from those third-party services. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect:**  
We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages and push notifications, to allow you to find others and have others find you on the Service, and to permit you to share content with others on the Service. Where you have given consent for us to use your personal data to provide certain Services, you may withdraw your consent for some uses of the data at any time by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5a3e3b2e3b2a28332c3b39231a2c3f2835743935). 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

We only use your information to provide you the Service. **We do not sell your information to Third Parties or use it for purposes unrelated to keeping the Service up and running for our users.**

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Legal basis for processing in the EU:**   
In the EU, the purposes for which we process your personal data are: 

1\. Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you for the Service; 

2\. Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests; and 

3\. Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation in the EU. 

We have set out in the table at **Annex 1** and **Annex 2** a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. Please contact us using the details above if you need information about the specific legal basis we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one legal basis has been set out. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

The main reason we use your information is to deliver and improve our Service, meaning to enable you to participate as a user in the Vero network by posting, commenting, liking, etc. 

Generally, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances: 

1\. Where we need to perform our obligations under the [Terms of Use](https://www.vero.co/terms-of-use), the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you for the Service; 

2\. Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests; and 

3\. Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. 

Please see Annex 1 and Annex 2 for more information about the legal basis we rely on to process your personal data. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Use of Cookies and Other Technology to Collect Information:**   
We, and our third party partners, automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our website or use our Service, read our emails, or otherwise engage with us. When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access the Service, and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. We may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access the Service. Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service. We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service. When you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification number associated with your device (“Device ID”), mobile carrier, device type and manufacturer, phone number, and location data (e.g., city and state) of your mobile device. We use or may use the data collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Service; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) otherwise to plan for and enhance our Service; and (g) automatically update the Vero application on your mobile devices. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

We may employ commonly-used Internet technologies like cookies to help remember you and to personalize and improve your experience on the Service. 

We only use the information collected from cookies to provide the Service to you and to improve your experience. We do not use advertising cookies, nor do we sell the information we collect through our cookies to advertisers (or any other third parties) or use it for advertising purposes. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Sharing of Your Information:**   
Remember, our Service allows you to connect with others and share information about yourself with other individuals. Your profile information, including your name, photo and other personal information you include in your bio, will be available publicly to other members of the Service by default. In addition, any User Content that you upload to the Service can be made publicly available if you choose to do so - we operate a feature that allows you to share a link to your profile, where your posts can be viewed publicly by non-users of the Service. This feature only works if you have made your profile or posts public. By using the Service, you consent to have your profile information displayed to other members of the Service. Consider your own privacy and personal safety when logging in to our Service and sharing your information with anyone. Vero never shares your phone number and email address with other users on the Service without your consent. 

We may also share your personal information with third parties who we require to operate, maintain and provide the features and functionalities of Service. Examples of these necessary third parties include: 

• Other companies owned by or under common ownership as Vero, which also includes our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control) or our ultimate holding company (i.e., any organization that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns; 

• Third party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us which may include providing payment, mailing or email services, tax and accounting services, data enhancement services, fraud prevention services, web hosting, and/or analytic services, email server services (to send messages to users), product development services and identity verification services. In addition, we share location data with Foursquare Labs Inc. ("Foursquare") to provide you with features of the Service. Foursquare may use your personal data for its own purposes. Please see Foursquare's privacy policy at <http://foursquare.com/legal/privacy> with more information about how Foursquare uses your personal data; 

• Third parties with whom we partner to provide contests and sweepstakes, which will usually be identified by name in the Official Rules of the contest or sweepstakes; 

• The public and other members of the Service at your request. Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. To change your privacy settings on the Service, please change your profile setting. Subject to your profile and privacy settings, any User Content that you make public is searchable by other Users. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other Users have copied or saved that information; and 

• With other members of the Service so that you can be “found” on the Service. When other members of the Service attempt to “Add Contacts” on the Service using their address book or by name search or user ID, we will identify you as an existing member of the Service if your contact information is in your friend’s address book. Similarly, we will let you know which of your contacts in your address book are already members of the Service based on the contact information associated with the member’s account. 

When we grant these necessary third parties access to your personal information, we require that they use your personal information solely in accordance with the rights granted to us and restrictions placed on us in this Privacy Policy. 

We may also share your information with other parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

When you create a profile on the Service, certain information – like your profile picture, name and other biographical information – is made available to the public by default. Although you can change your permissions for certain types of content, this basic biographical information will always be available to the public as long as you have an account on the Service. 

We share your personal information only with those third parties who are necessary for the provision, operation and maintenance of the Service. When we provide third parties access to your personal information, we require them to adhere to strict information security requirements – including requiring such third parties to act in compliance with this Privacy Policy and to access and use your personal information only as necessary to assist us in providing the Service. 

For the avoidance of doubt, we do not sell, grant access to, or otherwise share your personal information with advertisers or any third parties who aren’t our service providers. 

We may also share your information with third parties as required to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena/court order, legal process or other government request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Use, including the investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Vero, its users or the public as required or permitted by law and (v) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud or stalking), security or technical issues. 

We may though also share your information with third parties only as necessary to comply with the law and to enforce our rights. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**How We Store and Process Your Information:**   
**Storage and Processing:** Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States, United Kingdom, or any other country in which Vero or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that any personal data are treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Such transfers are made pursuant to appropriate safeguards. For more information regarding Vero's compliance with the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Privacy Shield Principles, please see our [Privacy Shield Privacy Statement](https://vero.co/vero-privacy-shield-statement). 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**How We Protect Your Information:**   
**Keeping your information safe:** Vero cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Vero, at all times. However, Vero cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Vero or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites and services that you add to the Vero Service, such as social networks. Vero is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.  
**Compromise of information:** In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Vero will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Your Choices About Your Information:**   
**Commercial and marketing communications:** We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We may send you emails containing newsletters, promotions and special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you will be given the option to opt out or change your preferences. We also use your information to send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). You may not opt out of Service-related emails. You will also be able to be “found” on Vero based on information that you provide (see “Adding Contacts on the Service”) above.   
**You control your account information and settings:** You may update your account information at any time by logging into your account and changing your settings. You can also stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests. As noted above, you may not opt out of Service-related communications (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a1c5c0d5c0d1d3c8d7c0c2d8e1d7c4d3ce8fc2ce).   
**Opting out:** The only way to completely opt out of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your mobile device or browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, located at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) ). Depending on your type of device, it may not be possible to delete or disable tracking mechanisms on your mobile device. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents Vero or its business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Service. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Service. If you have any questions about opting out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#77040207071805033701120518591418). 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

Where you have agreed for us to do so, we may send you messages to inform you about our newest features and special offers; however, we understand you may not want to get these, so you can unsubscribe from these messages at any time. 

However, there are certain communications about the Service that we need to send you, like important updates to the [Terms of Use](https://www.vero.co/terms-of-use) or Privacy Policy. You may not opt out of these messages. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Your rights in respect of your personal information if you are resident in the EU and Switzerland:**   
If you are located in the EU or Switzerland, you have the following rights in respect of your personal data that we hold: 

**a) Right of access.** The right to obtain access to your personal data. 

**b) Right to rectification.** The right to obtain rectification of your personal data without undue delay where that personal data is inaccurate or incomplete. 

**c) Right to erasure.** The right to obtain the erasure of your personal data without undue delay in certain circumstances, such as where the personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed. 

**d) Right to restriction.** The right to obtain the restriction of the processing undertaken by us on your personal data in certain circumstances, such as where the accuracy of the personal data is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of that personal data. 

**e) Right to portability.** The right to portability allows you to move, copy or transfer personal data easily from one organization to another. 

**f) Right to object.** You have a right to object to processing based on legitimate interests and direct marketing. 

**g) Right to withdraw consent.** You should be aware that you are entitled to withdraw your consent where that has been given, at any time. If you do this and we have no alternative lawful reason to process your personal data, this may affect our ability to provide you with rights to use the Service. 

If you wish to exercise one of these rights, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#086c697c69787a617e696b71487e6d7a67266b67). 

You also have the right to lodge a complaint to your local data protection authority. Further information about how to contact your local data protection authority is available at <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm>

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

If you are located in the EU or Switzerland, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data: 

a) Request access to your personal data. 

b) Request correction of your personal data. 

c) Request erasure of your personal data. 

d) Request restriction of processing your personal data. 

e) Request transfer of your personal data. 

f) Object to processing of your personal data. 

g) Right to withdraw consent. 

If you wish to exercise one of these rights, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**How Long Does Vero Keep Information About Me:**   
Following termination or deactivation of your User account, Vero may retain your profile information and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes. 

For individuals based in the EU or Switzerland, we store personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which we collect the data (see above under "WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU?"), except if required otherwise by law. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

For individuals based in the EU or Switzerland, we will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. 

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**“Do Not Track Signals”:**   
Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our customers, we are not able to respond to Do-Not-Track signals from your browser at this time. As discussed above, we track website usage information through the use of cookies for analytic and internal purposes only. Because we do not collect this information to track you across websites over time, your selection of the “Do Not Track” option provided by your browser will not have any effect on our collection of cookie information for analytics or internal purposes. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Children’s Privacy:**   
Vero does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#60131510100f1214201605120f4e030f). 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

Vero is only for users age 13 and up. Let us know if you believe we might have information from or about a child under the age of 13 so we can address this issue. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Links to Other Web Sites and Services:**   
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and we do not have any control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third-party access to your User Content you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service. 

WHAT WE’RE SAYING 

While our Service does link to other websites or services, we are not responsible for any of the information of content found there or for the information those websites or other services may collect from you. 

LEGAL TERMS OF USE 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**   
Vero may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page. 

_This Privacy Policy was last modified on July 20, 2018._

Personal information we may collect when you use the service.

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Contact information and basic personal details** such as your first name, last name, phone number, and email address and picture. 

HOW WE USE IT 

We use this information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features of the Service. 

We use this information to communicate with you, including sending Service-related communications (such as invoices and information about updates to the Service, and any news, alerts and marketing communications (in line with your settings and options)). 

We use this information to deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Service. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary: 

• for the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; 

• for our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service, for marketing purposes and communicating with users; and 

• with your consent, to provide you with certain features of the Service, such as verification of your account. 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service, for marketing purposes and communicating with users. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Profile and account information such as your** unique name, username, password, any additional information that you share with us such as your user biography, content such as photos and contacts names, contacts' user IDS and your connection to those IDs, connection to those contacts. Where you have chosen to do so, this information can be shared publicly with non-users of the Service. 

To add photos, you may allow us to access your camera or photo album. Some of the information you choose to provide us may be considered "special" or "sensitive" in certain jurisdictions, for example your racial or ethnic origins. By choosing to provide this information, you consent to our processing of that information. 

HOW WE USE IT 

We use this information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features of the Service (such as to create your profile/account) 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service. 

In the case of sensitive personal data, we will process this with your explicit consent. 

HOW WE USE IT 

We use this information to allow you to communicate with other users of Vero. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, in order to administer the Service). 

HOW WE USE IT 

To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy). 

HOW WE USE IT 

To manage our relationship with you which will include notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy; and communicate with you. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• compliance with our legal obligation. 

HOW WE USE IT 

To administer and protect our business, the Service, our website and your personal data (including security, fraud, troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, cybersecurity, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise); and 

• compliance with our legal obligation. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Location:** When you use the Service, we will collect and process information such as your city, country, ZIP/location. We use various technologies to determine location, including IP address, GPS and other sensors that may, for example, provide Vero with information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points and mobile towers. 

HOW WE USE IT 

We use this information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features of the Service (e.g., so that users can add location and photos of locations to posts). 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features of the Service. To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy). 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Payment and transaction information** including payment information (such as your credit or debit card details or your bank account details), and time, date and value of transactions. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to facilitate transactions and provide you with the Service. 

We use this information to provide customer support. 

We use this information to detect and prevent fraud. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract. 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service. 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely the detection and prevention of fraud. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Information provided by social networks, including Facebook, Twitter, Google+, when you connect to the Service.** The features and functionality of the Service connects social networks to the Service. In this case, we collect personal information from the social network in accordance with your privacy settings on that social network. The connected social network may provide us with information, such as your name, profile picture, network, gender, username, userID, age or age range, language, country, connections and any other information you have agreed it can share or that the social network provides to us. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We will use the personal information provided to allow you to log-in to the Service, to help create a public profile for you, and where we provide the functionality, we will also use the information provided to assist you in sharing the content you create, or your experiences on the Service with your contacts on the connected social network. 

**Please note:** If you have chosen to do this, your data will be governed by the privacy policy of that social network. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Communications.** If you contact our customer care team, we will collect the information you give us during the interaction. Sometimes, we monitor or record these interactions for training purposes and to ensure a high quality of service. Of course, we also process your messages with other users as well as the content you publish (e.g., information about music, books and movies), as part of the operation of the Service. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to maintain your profile and so that you can provide information about yourself. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to allow you to communicate with other users of Vero. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, in order to administer the Service). 

HOW TO USE IT 

To manage our relationship with you which will include notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy; and communicate with you. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and 

• compliance with our legal obligations. 

HOW TO USE IT 

To administer and protect our business, the Service, our website and your personal data (including security, fraud, troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service (namely, for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, cybersecurity, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise); and 

• compliance with a legal obligation. 

HOW TO USE IT 

To respond to requests from law enforcement 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for: 

• compliance with our legal obligations. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Information provided by third parties.** From time to time, we may receive information about you from users and third parties, for example, Facebook Connect, by “following,” “liking,” adding the Vero application, linking your account to the Service, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to Vero. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. We may obtain information from third parties to enhance or supplement our existing user information. We may also collect information about you that is publicly available. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We may combine this information with the information we collect from you directly. We use this information to contact you, to send you advertising or promotional materials or to personalise our Service, to pre-populate online forms, and to better understand the demographics of our users. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to tailor our Service to the user and to improve our Service generally. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**All personal information set out above.**

HOW TO USE IT 

We will use all the personal information we collect to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, to communicate with you, to monitor and improve our Service and business, and to help us develop new products and services. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to administer and improve the Service. 

Personal information collected automatically

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Information about how you access and use the Service** including, for example, how frequently you access the Service, the time you access the Service and how long you use the Service for, whether you access the Service from multiple devices, the website from which you came and the website to which you go when you leave the Service, and other actions you take on the Service. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to present the Service to you on your device. 

We use this information to administer the Service for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes, and to help us develop new products and services. 

We use this information to detect and prevent fraud. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to tailor the Service to the user and improve the Service generally. 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely communicating with users and responding to queries, complaints, and concerns, and for developing and improving the Service. 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely the detection and prevention of fraud. 

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**Information about your device** including information about the computer, tablet, smartphone or other electronic device you use to connect to the Website. This information can include details about the type of device, unique device identifying numbers, operating systems, browsers and applications connected to the Website through the device, your Internet service provider or mobile network, your IP address and your device's telephone number (if it has one). 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to present the Service to you on your device. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to tailor the Service to the user and improve the Service generally. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to administer the Service for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes, and to help us develop new products and services. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely communicating with users and responding to queries, complaints, and concerns, and for developing and improving the Service. 

HOW TO USE IT 

We use this information to detect and prevent fraud. 

LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely the detection and prevention of fraud.
